<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Open Network Infrastructure Association</title><link>https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Open Network Infrastructure Association</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Make Zurich hackathon</title><link>https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/make-zurich/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/make-zurich/</guid><description>The idea of running an event like MakeZurich starts out of a series of informal meetings between members of Open Data Zürich and The Things Network Zürich community.
Concept The concept of the event is to bridge the city government with the maker community by gathering problems and real needs of the public administration and exposing the community to them to foster fresh ideas and creative solutions.
Format The organizing team explored different formats for the event, ranging from a 6-months long open challenge, to a traditional 2-day hackathon.</description></item><item><title>The Things Network</title><link>https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/ttn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://opennetworkinfrastructure.org/projects/ttn/</guid><description>The Things Networkis building a network for the Internet of Things by creating abundant data connectivity, so applications and businesses can flourish.
The technology used is called LoRaWAN and it allows for things to talk to the internet without 3G or WiFi. So no WiFi codes and no mobile subscriptions.
It features low battery usage, long range and low bandwidth. Perfect for the internet of things.
Building a fully distributed internet of things data infrastructure LoRaWAN has the potential to enable an entire new class of use cases for the Internet of Things, but we need to open this up to the hacker/maker community.</description></item></channel></rss>